A makeover project
for your most unhinged leftovers.
The best chefs in Korea will
turn your fridge inside out.
The classy cooking show has returned.
-Chef & My Fridge!
-My Fridge!
Welcome to the show.
LET'S DO THIS
A NEW FACE!
We also have someone new with us.
Hello.
He shocked the culinary scene
with charcoal and meat.
HANDLING MEAT WITH FIRE AND WOOD
Known as Barbecue Lab Director
from Culinary Class Wars 2,
please welcome Yoo Yong-wook!
-Hello.
-Welcome.
HELLO, I'M THE NEW GUY
Wow.
Hello, yes.
I live for meat and die for meat, yes.
I'm Director Yoo Yong-wook,
who cooks with fire and smoke.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW
HEAD TILT
Why do you
call yourself a director and not a chef?
I've never learned to cook professionally.
I took it up as a hobby
while working a job
and named
a little nook in my farm "the lab."
And then, I opened a restaurant.
Since I was the director of my little lab,
I decided to go with that.
-How long did you keep the office job?
-My job?
Eight and a half years.
I worked at C company
in the food brand marketing team.
Then, many people
began to visit me at the lab,
so six years ago,
I decided to quit and open the restaurant.
-He's like Poong.
-It's a similar situation.
He gave up on webtoons--
-I didn't!
-You did.
-I didn't! It's a short hiatus.
-You didn't?
-People said, "You should be a chef!"
-Yes.
So I opened a café, but it went under.
LOL HAHA
-The café.
-Similar beginnings.
I can feel the connection.
We're both from the streets,
so we're eager to learn.
-Have you been to his restaurant?
-I have.
His food is so good.
-It was the most delicious beef I've had.
-Really?
The most delicious.
He even puts on a show
with the smoker right in front of you.
We received a tip.
One of the chefs here has already bullied
-Director Yong-wook.
-Bullied?
-It's a tip from our production crew.
-Who would do that?
WHO WAS IT?
I think I know.
I wouldn't call it "bullying."
-You just pointed this way.
-Wait, no.
SINGLING OUT THE CULPRIT
Wait, it's me?
HE'S QUICK TODAY
Sung-jun and I once
ran into each other at an event…
-What is it?
-…and we talked about this show.
He said,
"Chef & My Fridge is tough to break into."
SHOCKED
He said the chemistry
has already been established…
COLD STARE
…so even if I went on CCW2,
it'd be tough to break into this one.
-This was before he was on CCW2.
-Did he have to do that?
Why is he so conceited
outside of the show?
We need you to explain.
I was speaking on behalf of the writers.
-The writers? You aren't a writer!
-From our writers' shoes.
A few chefs here were anxious,
thinking we'd be let go after CCW2,
-and Nam-no and I were especially scared.
-He's right.
It must've been my defense mechanism.
Now that we've invited him here,
we won't have a moment of dead air
even if we let go of one person.
We're in a tight situation these days,
so why don't we let one go?
Let's turn it into a survival show.
SUGGESTING AN ELIMINATION MATCH
Let's open up a minor league.
We might,
with the network's financial difficulties.
WE'VE BEEN STRUGGLING LATELY…
-What if our set disappears?
-We can't go on TV.
If anyone suddenly disappears,
just think, "Oh, they're gone."
That might happen.
It's time to meet today's fridge owners.
Both guests today
are legends in their own fields.
IS THAT SO?
Please welcome today's fridge owners!
Come on out!
Today's fridge owners!
A PASSIONATE WELCOME
TODAY'S FRIDGE OWNERS
Chang Hang-jun and J. Y. Park!
Welcome to the show! Please meet everyone.
THIS IS HUGE
CONTINUOUSLY AMAZED♥
I'm so jealous. He has long arms.
We're here with two legends.
Our show feels even more validated.
-Of course.
-Let me introduce this guest.
The happiest filmmaker in Korea right now
who became a cinematic legend
after his production of The King's Warden.
Please welcome Director Chang Hang-jun!
Hello.
Welcome.
Please say hello to our viewers too.
Hello.
A world-renowned Korean cinematic legend…
CALLS HIMSELF A LEGEND?
…screenwriter Kim Eun-hee's husband,
Chang Hang-jun.
THE ROMANTIC LEGEND INTRODUCES HIMSELF
-Allow me to introduce him.
-Sure.
Personally, I'm a huge fan.
A genius artist
and music producer,
the legend of K-pop.
-Please welcome J. Y. Park!
-J. Y. Park!
Please say hello to our viewers.
Hello, everyone.
JYP is here!
THE LEGEND'S SHORT AND SWEET INTRO
-Half air, half sound.
-He's so cool.
THE ENERGY ALREADY PICKS UP
JUST AFTER THE INTRODUCTIONS
From what we know,
this is the first time you two
have sat together for a meal.
-Yes, it's our first time meeting.
-Yes.
-In real life?
We're sitting here in the moment
as the two legends meet.
A HISTORICAL MOMENT
It's belated, but congrats
-on surpassing ten million admissions.
-Thank you.
I've watched it three times.
-You have?
-Yes.
Twice with my mother,
and once with my wife.
And I cried a river
every single time I watched it.
The casting was spot-on.
Yes, that is something
-I also deem a great achievement.
-Right?
It was the first film in a while
that made me cry.
-It rarely happens, but it was touching.
-Right?
"You must cross the river now!"
And Park Ji-hoon's eyes!
I thought, "Hang-jun did
such a great job at casting him."
THE NARRATIVE ENDS WITH A COMPLIMENT
Here's what I've been feeling lately
with everyone calling me
a cinematic legend and whatnot.
It kind of feels like
a huge act of collective mockery.
-No way. It's not.
-What is this?
A huge act of collective mockery.
I mean, I kept thinking about it
and still didn't think I was a legend.
I never knew my work would be
so deeply loved by the people
in such late years of my life.
It somehow turned into this huge syndrome,
but to be frank,
I'm someone who doesn't like seeing
one dominant player more than anybody.
Something that takes a huge lead
and leaves second place behind
where you can't even see them.
He always insulted those people.
I was like Koo Kyo-hwan's character
in We Are All Trying Here.
I'd say, "What an awful film.
How did they get the project?"
-"How is this good?"
-You did that?
I used to be in that position.
What's more important is that
thanks to this film,
many have found the fun
in going to the theaters again.
We were all reminded that it was a place
for a group cultural experience.
NODDING
And after my film, people went to see
many other Korean films too,
so the industry is booming,
along with the movie theater business.
I'm most thrilled that more opportunities
will be available to my colleagues.
We received a tip
from one of your close associates.
"He has become a different man
after bringing in ten million admissions."
What do you mean, Poong?
-What?
-Here's the thing.
Previously, when I had plans
to meet him for drinks,
-I couldn't wait for that day.
-Right.
He was the most hilarious person I knew.
I thought,
"How much funnier will he be today?"
-How can I put this?
-He's right.
-He was like a stand-up comedian.
-He's a big talker?
He'd even bring a stranger
and tell me that his friend
had been feeling down lately.
Yes, I brought my friend.
-I brought them.
-Someone who was down in the dumps?
BECAME A COPING MEETING
And when he did,
-I'd do a rabbit dance…
-He was insane.
…and start juggling.
He performed musical numbers by himself.
He sang songs. He is no joke.
I think it began
at six million admissions.
He suddenly became very dull
during our get-togethers.
-He talked less and became boring.
-Actually,
my wife, screenwriter Kim Eun-hee,
is quite faint-hearted.
She said, "Hang-jun,
be careful what you say out there."
"It may seem like
people are crazy about you right now,
but they'll all turn on you
the moment you slip up."
Whenever I had to talk,
I had to think that people had
a flower in one hand
and a stone in the other.
A FLOWER AND A STONE, ONE IN EACH HAND
Even when they throw flowers at you,
it's still too much for you to handle.
And one day, the moment you slip,
they begin to throw the stones,
and you don't even know the reason.
-True.
-That's why
Eun-hee told me to be careful.
She said, "Hang-jun,
you are prone to behave rashly."
-You're prone to that.
-"Your words will cause trouble."
So I wanted to be careful with my words.
So my friends are quite disappointed
-because now I'm boring.
-Seriously. He's really boring.
-Time will have to pass.
-He'll have to botch three films
to recover from this dullness.
I'm waiting for his next film to flop.
-Thanks.
-So he's been showing self-control.
-What's this about?
-Yes?
You didn't know the film would do so well
and didn't sign a backend deal,
so you couldn't earn a lot?
-That was scripted for a mockumentary.
-It was a mockumentary.
It was the storyline for that thing.
-So I ended up…
-He always makes sure he comes out ahead.
He would never.
-He's good with these things.
-The film was a huge hit,
-but we heard you didn't make a lot.
-No?
I like having that kind of public image.
DOESN'T GO OUT OF HIS WAY TO CORRECT IT♥
I think it's nice to arouse
people's sympathy and pity.
As you know,
I'm in other programs too, right?
He'd call me and ask,
"Hey, how much do you get paid?"
He always asks me that.
-He's good with that.
-It's because
I was right next to him
when he got the offer for this show.
-When he was on the phone.
-He was next to me.
-I see.
-So I asked,
-"What was that?"
He said,
"I got an offer from a program like this."
I said, "Yes, I see."
"So how much are they paying?"
IMPORTANT
-He wasn't well-off back then.
-No, I wasn't.
-It was around a million won, I think.
-Was it? I don't remember.
So I said, "Ask for 1.05 million won."
-Ask for 1.05 million? 50,000 won more?
-And I asked,
"What if they drop the offer
because of that?"
-He said, "No, not over 50,000 won."
-Never.
It's one thing if they had never called,
but they wouldn't call it off
just because they don't want
to give you 50,000 won more.
-I've also been tight financially.
-Of course.
Let's say I got an offer to do a TV show
for 400,000 won. Then I'd ask,
-"Give me 20,000 won more."
-That's it.
-I only ask for 5% more.
-Yes.
It'd be kind of weird to say no.
-You're right.
-It's true.
That was why he told me to ask for more.
-That's why it was 50,000 won.
-It's 5%.
-You can't ask for more than 5%.
-It has to be 5%.
And with that difference, the 5%,
I made a bank account for my daughter
and left it there.
-For her?
-Yes.
-I see.
-That was what you did.
I'M SO DEEPLY MOVED…
-J. Y. Park had a favor to ask you.
-Really?
I starred in
a KBS drama called Dream High.
They said I was a good actor,
that I wasn't half bad.
After that, I suddenly got to play
the lead role in a film.
-Suddenly?
-A Millionaire on the Run.
I watched it at the theater!
I felt a bit of pressure
to play the lead role so soon,
and I shouldn't have done it!
"A MILLIONAIRE ON THE RUN FLOPS
WITH 100,000 ADMISSIONS"
After that film flopped,
I never received another offer,
not even one.
WAS FORCED TO GIVE UP ON ACTING…
I knew I could revive this career
if I took up a comical supporting role.
So back there, I tried to ask him
about the next project.
Your film
was really moving.
Thank you very much.
Do you have an idea
of what your next project will be?
No, not completely.
-Are there a few?
-I've narrowed them down.
It'll probably be something dark
yet suspenseful.
…something dark yet suspenseful.
I'm out.
WHY?
-He's doing something dark.
-For the next project?
Are you already planning your next step?
Yes, I've been
looking into a few projects.
-This is how cautious I am now.
-Yes.
Back in the day,
-I would've been yapping about it already.
-In the old days,
he would've yapped
even before the shooting
-and we stopped him.
-Everyone in his life would know.
-We would've had to stop him.
-Yes.
Who could you have played
in The King's Warden?
I think…
I'm not saying I'm that good.
-Just the acting style.
-The style.
Yoo Hai-jin's role.
I agree.
THAT STYLE
I'm nowhere near his level.
I don't want any hate.
-I'm just saying our styles are similar.
-The styles.
He says this, but the article will read,
"J. Y. Park,
'I can act as well as Yoo Hai-jin.'"
BREAKING:
"MY ACTING IS ON THE LEVEL OF YOO HAI-JIN"
Yes! That's it!
-That's what happens.
-That he's…
ENDS UP GETTING STONED
"I should've played Eom Heung-do."
-"I should've been Eom Heung-do."
-"I could've played Eom Heung-do."
THAT ROLE SHOULD'VE BEEN MINE
You've given us your fridge today,
so we're about to go through
the fridge of a cinematic legend,
Director Chang Hang-jun.
How many people use this fridge?
-My mother-in-law is the main user.
-Your mother-in-law?
-So you must live with her.
-Yes.
Then it's my daughter and me,
the three of us.
Ms. Kim Eun-hee
usually eats and sleeps in her studio.
So she does not keep a lot in there.
Whenever you mention your wife,
you use the highest honorifics
in the third person.
That way, I can cultivate a great image
among netizens.
He gets nice comments too.
HE'S THE BEST HUSBAND
HE'S SUCH A GREAT HUSBAND
So you must know a lot about this fridge.
-Yes, and I fill it up when we run low.
-You fill it up too?
After talking to your mother-in-law?
I always loved the feeling
of restocking household essentials.
I'd go to the supermarket
and look for olive oil
that's 20 won cheaper per liter.
FRUGAL
That's not going to make me rich,
but there's fun in knowing
that I spent money most efficiently.
-Right.
-It feels good.
-The small happiness.
-Yes, I enjoy that.
What did your mother-in-law say
when you told her you needed this?
-Yes, I wonder.
-She must've been worried.
She was quite flustered.
We hold prejudice
and believe that
all mothers are organized.
It's not true.
BREAKING THE STEREOTYPE
That's what most people think, I guess.
That all mothers are organized.
My mother-in-law
is someone who had a rough time
raising three daughters alone,
so she tends to stay frugal.
Instead of cleanliness and sanitation,
her focus is on food preservation.
SPECIALIZES IN FOOD PRESERVATION
After all,
she lived through the Korean War.
CAN CONNECT
In case of an emergency,
she'll pull them out.
In case of emergency?
So this fridge is always ready.
-Yes, for emergencies.
-In case of all kinds of emergencies.
When she heard that
the production crew would take the fridge,
she became alarmed
and began to clean it.
She worked on it a little.
-She did.
-She was conscious of the show.
-The mother-in-law's warden.
-The mother-in-law's warden?
Let's open up Hang-jun's fridge.
What does he keep inside?
We present Hang-jun's fridge!
All right.
It's organized.
PRESENTING HANG-JUN'S FRIDGE
She must've thrown out a lot.
She must've gone through everything.
First off, I see some alcohol
on the very top shelf.
-Some soju.
-Yes.
-And beer.
-And some wine over here.
-That's right.
Do you enjoy alcohol?
Actually, I don't drink much at home.
I don't drink at home,
but when I order delivery food,
I'm sometimes a bit short
of the minimum amount.
So I add a bottle of soju to my order,
which my mother-in-law uses to cook,
-and so do I, sometimes.
-That's why.
So soju is usually for cooking.
-What about beer?
-We keep beer
for Eun-hee when she comes home,
because she drinks it as she works.
-As for the wine, I drink it occasionally.
-Occasionally.
Do you not drink beer?
At some point in time,
I stopped drinking it.
I see. When was that point in time?
After I got a small break.
One day, he suddenly began
to show up with a bottle of wine.
-So here's the order.
-Yes.
He began with soju, then beer,
and after surpassing
17 million admissions…
-His break.
-…he switched to wine.
I don't have it here,
but I've been drinking whiskey.
Whiskey.
THE LEGEND'S TASTE
You must have some memories about beer.
This was when my wife and I
took out a lease
on our very first house.
-It was a tiny little place.
-Right.
When we got the key to the house
from the real estate agent,
we realized that
because we have this key now,
no one is allowed in
without our permission,
be it the President or the Pope.
When we opened the door
and walked into the empty and dusty house,
I said,
"Eun-hee, let's grab some newspapers."
So we grabbed recycled newspapers,
beer, and shrimp-flavored snacks.
-How romantic.
-We put them down,
turned on the heater because it was cold,
then continued to drink some more.
After that, we fell asleep,
woke up, and began to drink again.
I remember that day.
-That was your housewarming party.
-Right.
-These must be…
-Side dishes.
…his mother-in-law's side dishes.
And some fish. Pomfrets.
-Pomfrets?
-You have pomfrets?
Do you enjoy seafood?
Yes, I love seafood.
My mother-in-law makes
delicious, braised fish.
HER SPECIALTY, BRAISED POMFRET
-She likes to make that.
-Deliciously-seasoned.
-We like to eat it very spicy.
-Very spicy.
We like to keep
quite a lot of seafood around.
If you keep them in the freezer,
in case of an emergency…
Right.
-In case of an emergency.
-Preparation.
CAUTIOUS
I also…
Can I share this?
-Yes.
-Sure.
When my wife, our kid, and I eat together,
the two of them still can't debone fish.
So I'd pick out the meat,
then give it to Eun-hee and my daughter.
In the end, I only eat the leftovers
on the bones, like a mother.
That's all.
SELF-PRAISE, THE END
What did he mean by that?
-You're good at praising yourself…
-Yes.
-…so we'll give you more chances.
-Really?
Is there a dish you're good at making?
My friends tried my dish and said,
"Hey, I've had lots of pasta,
but this is the best one I've ever had."
-Whoa.
-He makes good pasta.
Something like aglio e olio.
-Or tteokguk.
-Rice cake soup?
That's my wife's favorite dish
among everything I've made.
Here's a thing I learned about cooking.
Are you all listening?
SURE… WE'RE LISTENING…
There was this moment when I realized
the act of cooking
is something rather noble.
-As a chef…
-Right.
…you're fulfilling other people's hunger
and satisfying their appetites.
Whenever I cook for my daughter
or mother-in-law, I can't help but look
-to see if they're enjoying it.
-Yes.
-We do that.
-It's nice to hear that it's delicious.
That was something I've felt.
-The next one.
-The next shelf.
I see something unusual here.
-Korean beef spinal cord.
-Spinal cord?
That's an epicure-level ingredient.
What is this?
What are these?
Is that monkfish liver?
-It's monkfish liver! Yes.
-Monkfish liver.
It's called ankimo in Japanese.
What's this?
-Pi-sundae.
-Korean blood sausage.
-Do you enjoy offal?
-I do.
I prefer offal to regular meat,
and quite obsessively.
-Obsessively?
-Yes.
We say someone
is as bizarre as A Dog's Life
when they like to eat bizarre food
that makes ordinary people go, "Why?"
Film director Park Chan-wook
is one of the bizarre ones.
I'm also one of them,
so I love something like offal,
or skin…
Byproducts.
Tail.
Fish head.
Beef tongue. Something like that.
Not the ordinary kind of meat,
but the minor league of the meat.
When we were newlyweds,
my wife said,
"What do you want to eat? I'll cook."
-Gopchang?
-Gopchang-jeongol?
I asked, "Honestly?" She said, "Yes."
I said, "Raw liver."
LOVES RAW LIVER♥
So she brought me
a huge serving of raw liver.
-I thought he'd eat like a child.
-Not at all.
J. Y. Park, do you
also like meat byproducts?
I like it selectively.
-Selectively?
-Yes.
Gopchang and makchang,
grilled intestine.
-So good.
-They're so good.
I can't eat the liver
that comes with sundae.
You don't like those.
Offal is the sexiest kind of food.
Do you keep lots of these here
because you eat them at home?
Well, no, because it's not easy
to cook offal at home.
I heard you'd make
something delicious for me here,
so I got some at a nearby supermarket.
There are lots more over here.
Small intestine. Seasoned large intestine.
Small intestine, large intestine.
Those are the ones I already had.
What's next?
Herbal medicine.
He has some herbal medicine.
-Herbal medicine.
-Peace of Mind Herbal Medicine.
When Chef & My Fridge said
you'd come for my fridge,
I didn't think
you'd literally take everything,
including my herbal medicine.
So I couldn't take it today.
-Do you want it?
-Would you like one?
-I haven't even opened it.
-Right.
You haven't even opened this one.
-I should take one.
-Please take a pouch.
Can you cut this for me?
HANG-JUN IS HIGH-MAINTENANCE
-You can cut it open like this.
-There's an opening.
I know.
But it keeps dripping.
It drips, so he wants to cut it.
RIPPING
DIDN'T HEAR HIM
SULLEN HANG-JUN
THIS ISN'T IT…
GULPING
He's been too busy lately,
so he's now in need
of herbal medicine.
-Why does it look good?
-Right?
-My mouth began to water.
-He became
a little mad this morning
because we took his medicine.
I mean, listen.
You can't even use this to cook.
You can.
-Really?
-To cook pig's trotters.
I SEE…
Achyranthes and chicken feet extract.
-Chicken feet extract?
That's my mother-in-law's.
-I heard it's good for your joints.
-Yes.
She said
her son-in-law
keeps restocking this extract
and never lets it run out.
Yes, I order
every health supplement she takes
long before she runs out of them
and restock everything.
When our crew went to take your fridge,
your mother-in-law sat them down
-and told them how proud she was of you.
-I see.
So they wrote it down.
These are the things about Hang-jun
that she's proud of.
We'll read it word-for-word.
"My son-in-law is famous,
yet he's frugal
and has a great character."
"He never complains about food,
is always considerate,
and is always kind even at home."
"I've lived with him for 19 years,
but there is zero inconvenience."
"I don't have a son of my own,
but even if I did,
I'd love my son-in-law more."
"My son-in-law is my happiness."
We wrote down exactly what she said.
She really is very fond of me.
This happened when we were newlyweds.
She used to work
as a yogurt delivery woman.
And this was way back,
when she'd end up making
ten won per bottle she delivered.
One day, I picked up a call
from a number I didn't know,
and she said, "It's me, Hang-jun."
I said, "Is that you, Mother?"
"Hang-jun, just listen without responding.
Are you doing well?"
She tells me to listen
and asks a question.
THAT'S TRUE…
I said, "Sure," but she went,
"No, just listen. Are you doing okay?"
And then, the phone went dead.
I later found out that
because she was so frugal,
she'd notice pay phones
that still had minutes left
and would call me.
-We'd leave the receiver up.
-She called me…
-I'm about to cry.
-…just to hear my voice,
because we weren't living together.
There was no inconvenience
even after we moved in with her.
She even said her son-in-law
is better than her daughter.
I also agree with that.
VERY PROUDLY
She adores me a lot,
and she does a lot for me too,
like always making me breakfast.
Like a son.
I wouldn't say I'm a good son-in-law,
but it's just that
she's a great mother-in-law.
A great mother-in-law?
I've never seen a mother-in-law
who's so devoted.
I thought he said hyomo,
yeast when making beer.
There are lots of vegetables too.
Sweet potato stems, carrots, chwinamul.
And some fruit.
Do you like fruits and veggies?
-I love vegetables.
-He does.
I feel my body awakening
whenever I eat veggies,
but fruit, not so much.
Why not?
-No one in my family enjoys fruit.
-No fruit.
Because it's sweet?
-I don't like sweet things.
-He doesn't.
I see.
The reason why we have those
is because my mother-in-law got some
to look presentable
since it's going to be shown on TV.
So you usually don't have those?
Rich people always have fruit at home.
-Something like that.
-So your mother-in-law bought some?
But she said you'd eat tomatoes.
-I like tomatoes.
-You do eat tomatoes?
-It's a vegetable.
-I found out that it was a vegetable.
Next, the freezer.
-Shrimp.
-Yes.
Female blue crabs.
-Yes, blue crabs.
-Pre-cut female blue crabs.
One of my best dishes
is ggotge-tang, spicy blue crab stew.
-I see.
-I see. You can make ggotge-tang?
A great bar snack.
On the day I make that dish,
everyone comes home.
-To eat it?
-Yes.
At times,
it even includes my brothers-in-law.
We have to finish everything on that day.
You can also see
these shelf-stable ingredients.
That was all for Hang-jun's fridge!
FINISHED CHECKING OUT HANG-JUN'S FRIDGE
What kind of dishes
is he looking to eat today?
Let's see what his orders are. Show us!
-The Offal's Warden.
-Not The King's Warden.
-After all, we all are offal's warden.
-True.
We all must live with our insides.
Instead of the usual grilled offal,
I want to eat something
that you make in your own style,
something new and different.
-Nothing ordinary.
-No.
What's the next order?
-A Dish for Exhausted Hang-jun.
He must be exhausted these days.
-He's even taking herbal medicine.
-That's true.
It isn't the kind of life I wanted.
-Not this much.
-There's so much attention.
I'm drained physically and mentally.
As you've seen, I'm taking
herbal medicine for my energy anyway.
So instead of something healthy,
I want something that makes me go,
"Wow, this is so new! It's so good!"
Something that just tastes good
-to make you happy.
-Yes.
A dish that'll make him
happy and cheerful.
We're here today with ten chefs,
so one of the rounds
must be played as a team.
If they must play as a team,
I personally want to see
the Chinese sister chefs work together.
The possessed sisters.
-That's a great idea.
-I'd love to.
-I'm in.
-Me too. We'll do the team round.
I thought you'd make a good team.
-Their opponent would be so annoyed.
-They seem tough.
I wonder how energetic they'll be.
-Let's do this.
-So first, it's the Chinese sister chefs.
We need another team.
Do any two of you have good teamwork?
-I'd like to join.
-Sung-jun?
SURPRISED
Last episode, I was destroyed
by Chef Moon-jung in an attempt
to take my sixth straight win.
I haven't been able to sleep
since that day,
-so I want to get my revenge today.
-To beat Moon-jung?
-Are you teaming up with Nam-no?
-No, I don't want to.
-I don't think I'll do that.
-Okay.
I thought it'd be great if I did it
-with Hyun-suk, my first master.
-All of a sudden?
-He wasn't even thinking about it.
-That was so random.
Well, you know…
FLUSTERED AT THE RANDOMNESS
You don't seem too thrilled.
I'm really not.
Yes, you don't seem thrilled.
Sung-jun isn't the type
who can easily work with someone else.
…AGREED
But if it's against those two,
I am willing to take that tough journey.
-Someone must stop Chef Moon-jung.
-We must stop her.
Moon-jung and Eun-yeong are a team
and Sung-jun and Hyun-suk are a team.
The two teams can jump in
and take the order first.
I'll say it.
-I'm not particularly into offal, either.
-I like it, though.
-He doesn't negotiate.
-But I'm creative
-and he seems to like that.
-I like offal.
I want to make something
that can potentially inspire him.
Shouldn't you ask the other three
for their agreement?
Shouldn't you ask?
-I like offal.
-Actually,
he didn't ask before choosing me,
so I also won't ask and choose that round.
-I like offal, though.
-This is how we communicate.
Have some offal later.
They don't discuss anything.
That's where they want to go.
We're expected
to make him happy with our food,
so it sounds like our round.
EXCITED
That means the second round
will be the team round.
The Offal's Warden.
-I'll go.
-I knew it.
NAM-NO IS UP FOR THE CHALLENGE
-I like offal.
-I believe
offal is the sexiest kind of ingredient.
-Sexy.
-Sexy food.
You aren't picking what you want to eat.
You're trying to cook for Hang-jun.
-I understood.
-You did?
-We have to check with him a few times.
-We do.
Who wants to make an offal dish?
We won't force you into it.
-Ho-young.
-It suits him too.
I probably have more visceral fat
-around my organs.
-Visceral fat?
-Wait, visceral fat?
-He's nothing.
A NECK-AND-NECK MATCH HAS BEEN MADE
Let us begin
the first round of 15-minute cook-off
between Nam-no and Ho-young!
THE OFFAL ROUND BEGINS NOW
This is the first cook-off
played with Hang-jun's ingredients.
The body fat's warden, Chef Yoon Nam-no,
versus the visceral fat's warden,
Chef Jung Ho-young.
The two are up for the challenge.
-The thing is, Chef Nam-no…
-Yes, right.
We're well over halfway
through the year now,
in mid-July, but he still has one star.
-Yes.
-Huh? Is he new?
Moon-jung joined us last month,
but she already has three stars.
The problem with him is that
he looks like he'd cook up a mean dish.
That's it.
The expectation rises.
I've come to realize
that he doesn't make
something the guest wants to eat,
-but something that he wants to eat.
-That too.
That's why he hasn't won more.
Can't argue with that.
Whenever the fridge owner eats,
-he's only looking to eat the leftovers.
-Whatever he made.
He makes huge batches.
-He makes way too much food.
-Yes, it's way too much.
LOL
Ho-young said he'd like to let him win,
but this order
is just too advantageous for him.
-Really?
-Is that the case?
Yes, the place
I worked part-time for three years
during my studies in Japan
was a barbecue place
that specialized in offal.
Because I worked there,
This round is my area of expertise,
-so I don't think I'll lose.
-He just can't lose.
-Right.
-Some say you splurged what you made
over those three years
in eating offal there.
You're right.
I'm composed of half udon and half offal.
-It was half ramen last time.
-Half offal?
But Chef Nam-no,
you also said you felt confident
about this round.
I've also lived my life
eating a fair amount of offal.
-I see.
-I can see it.
Offal dishes taste delicious
even when it's sour or sweet.
-Sour offal?
-Seasoned with vinegar?
-Because you've had lots of it.
-Because of that,
I'm highly experienced.
Actually, when you're on the job,
you rarely end up eating it.
-He probably only knows how to make it.
-Sure.
But that's what's important.
Wait a second.
You have to cook, not eat.
-He only cares about what he'll eat.
-You have to make it.
-It's for the guest.
-It's not competitive eating!
OH, GOSH
Don't make it sweet, though.
CHEF HO-YOUNG'S INGREDIENTS:
BEEF SPINAL CORD, BEEF SMALL INTESTINE
BEEF LARGE INTESTINE, BEEF HEART,
MONKFISH LIVER, MORNING GLORY, AND MORE
First off, Chef Ho-young.
What are you making?
The name of my dish is
Chef &…
My Offal!
Offal!
CHEF & MY OFFAL
That was funny.
That sound was so clear.
This sound.
-Chef & My Offal.
SUMMONING THE SEAL CLAP
LOVING IT
-The sound was different.
-That sound.
It sounds so clear.
Pure and clear.
A makeover project for offal,
-I want to make a classy offal dish.
-Sure.
I'll use doenjang
-and grill the offal.
-Doenjang.
I'll turn monkfish liver into thick sauce
and pour it all over the top
to let you enjoy them together.
Lastly, I'll stir-fry
some morning glory and put it on top.
That sounds good.
Chef & My Offal.
VERY PLEASED
-You're good at making this look funny.
-He is.
EVERYONE JOINS HIM
It sounds like a water balloon.
CHEF NAM-NO'S INGREDIENTS:
BEEF SPINAL CORD, BEEF SMALL INTESTINE
LARGE INTESTINE, PI-SUNDAE, POLLACK ROE,
SEA CUCUMBER INTESTINES, AND MORE
You're up against him, Nam-no.
The name also better be good.
-You should've gone first.
-Nam-no.
-He should have.
-What are you making?
The dish I'm making is this.
Saved You in My Offal.
-Saved You…
-In My Offal.
HAHA
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S SAVED YOU IN MY OFFAL
That's something Park Ji-hoon coined
in his early career as a K-pop star.
THE CORRECT WAY OF SAVING
How are you going to save them?
-Saved You in My Offal?
-I plan to use
every single type of offal he has.
First, I'll make a cold dish.
I'll mix spinal cord
with salted pollack roe…
-What?
-…and serve it
with vinegar and soy sauce
made with tomatoes.
-Next, I'm making jeongol.
-Jeongol, offal hot pot.
In 15 minutes?
-He'd love that.
-Yes.
This is a soup dish
-that you can't say no to.
-Right.
I plan to make it taste light and clean
by mixing it with seafood-based broth.
-You do like soup dishes, right?
-I do.
His mouth watered as Nam-no spoke,
so he had to gulp right now.
I'm looking forward
to the cold spinal cord dish.
-What will that look like?
-Right.
-We usually eat it with just oil or sauce.
-Yes, sesame oil.
-What will that dish be like?
-You got some points.
So what's the name again?
Saved You in My Offal.
EVEN SAVING SOME FUN
He seems pleased.
Please give us the timer for 15 minutes.
Once the timer begins to tick,
we cannot stop.
Let us begin this round,
The Offal's Warden.
The offal he has consumed to this day
amounts to 1.5 tons.
The legend among big eaters,
Chef Jung Ho-young.
He saluted, thinking it was him.
The legend among big eaters.
The offal he has consumed this day
amounts to ten million admissions,
the legendary binge eater,
Chef Yoon Nam-no.
Which chef will become
the legend in the world of offal dishes?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
-Begin!
-Let's do this!
-Whoa.
-Take a good look.
You have to keep
a close eye on them starting now.
CHEF NAM-NO USES TOMATOES,
HANG-JUN'S FAVORITE
Aren't they too big?
He's using lots of tomatoes.
That's one too many tomatoes. Wait, why?
Why are you making so much?
He's making it for two.
That guy
is cooking his portion too.
-How much sauce are you making?
-Is that for one person?
You aren't saving it for winter.
He's making juice.
-He's juicing them.
-Oh, juicing?
Then he'll need a lot.
He's turning the tomatoes into juice.
-Looks good.
-That's already 30 seconds?
STARTS WITH THE SAUCE
Doenjang.
1. MIX DOENJANG, BULGOGI MARINADE,
OLIGOSACCHARIDE SYRUP, MINCED GARLIC
What are you making, Ho-young?
A doenjang-based sauce.
The sauce.
He throws the small intestines right in.
And large intestines.
Wow.
Are you eliminating the funky smell?
Yes, and it brings out the umami.
-That's how he eliminates the odd smell.
-Red pepper powder.
He spent three years
learning this in Osaka!
2. MIX OFFAL WITH THE SEASONING
The sauce is often made with doenjang.
YOU'RE ALREADY GRILLING IT?
Already?
-Already?
-You're already throwing it in?
-Large intestines.
-Large intestines?
-Those are very delicious.
Will you grill them over charcoal
after pan-frying them?
Yes, I'll pan-fry them first,
-and then on the gridiron.
-On the gridiron too.
It's only been a minute and a half,
but he's already pan-frying them.
-It's been a minute and a half now.
-Yes.
NAM-NO PREPS THE ONION
Look at him chopping.
IN IDENTICAL SIZES!
That's nicely chopped.
-Nam-no is slicing garlic.
-Slicing.
-But why so much?
-That's too much garlic.
-It needs lots of garlic.
-That's so much.
He would only need two cloves or so
if it were just for one serving.
2. COOK ONION AND GARLIC IN OIL
-Just an FYI, Hang-jun also loves garlic.
-I do.
-Large intestines.
-Small intestine. That should smell.
Are you not doing anything
to get rid of the meaty smell?
I added lots of garlic.
That was why he needed so much.
He's cooking them in garlic oil.
-Looks good.
-Not a bad idea.
-That's too much.
-As if he's cooking for the whole school.
I'm making broth with these.
-Soy sauce. Ginger.
-Ginger.
Garlic and ginger.
BECOME DELICIOUS!
They'll taste smoky and delicious.
Cooking wine.
I'll cook today
like my life depends on it.
He's cooking the large intestines.
-That looks good.
-Wow.
-Pi-sundae.
-Sundae.
-Is that pi-sundae?
-Yes, he had that.
Yes, I'm only using offal.
-You'll keep hearing questions like these.
-Really?
So you need to stay concentrated
and keep your ears open as you cook,
because you'll have to answer
the questions too.
What did you just throw in, Nam-no?
-What did you just add?
-Broth tablet.
-I have to answer everything?
-Yes, every question.
My gosh.
Can you add that deep flavor
to the jeongol broth in 15 minutes?
Right? His soup needs that deep flavor.
If he were making stew, it's fine,
but he's making a hot pot.
What's that? Chunjang, black bean paste?
What did you just add?
Green plum ssamjang.
-Green plum ssamjang.
-Sounds good.
-He's making offal jeongol right now.
-Oh, he's making jeongol.
Ho-young is pressing monkfish liver
-through a sieve.
-Monkfish liver?
He's pressing it through?
-That's monkfish liver?
-Yes.
There's a kind of broth
made with sieved monkfish liver
mixed with doenjang.
-Really?
-This is the soup base.
Monkfish liver
looks similar to doenjang from this far.
You're going to boil them together?
Oh, he's using that instant beef soup.
USE JUST THE SOUP!
That's soegogi-muguk, beef radish soup.
5. BOIL MONKFISH LIVER, BEEF RADISH SOUP,
GARLIC, DOENJANG, AND RED PEPPER POWDER
Take note that
Hang-jun likes his food spicy.
-He does? Something spicy?
-Yes.
-He likes spicy food.
-Spicy food.
Hot pepper.
Yes! Throw the hot peppers in! Excellent!
Yes, he likes his food spicy.
Both chefs are chopping hot peppers
as soon as they hear that
he likes spicy food.
They're adding piles of hot pepper.
He's now grilling
garlic cloves on the gridiron.
He's char-grilling
onion, green onion, and garlic.
-The small intestines look good.
-Those look great too.
Don't small intestines become tough
-when it's cooked for too long?
-It gets tough.
You're down to about eight minutes.
Seven minutes have gone by.
Nam-no chops scallions into thin slices.
Those are so thin.
Very thin.
What are those for?
-Toppings?
-Do they have to be so thin?
It's for the salad.
-Salad? Oh, the cold dish?
-The cold dish.
SCALLION, CHEONGYANG PEPPER
Ho-young preps the morning glory.
AND HE MINCES THE GARLIC…
Wait, he's chopping like Poong.
People do that in Southeast Asia…
-Yes.
-…to bring out the texture.
-Into uneven pieces.
-I think it's done for the texture.
OYSTER SAUCE
These will be the topping.
He cooks morning glory with garlic.
Morning glory stir-fry?
I guess he's making
a char-grilled style dish.
-Classic.
-Yes, it's the classic.
WHAT'S THIS?
Chef Nam-no picked up the tomato juice.
The tomato juice. What's it for?
Soy sauce?
Tomato juice and soy sauce?
What?
-I've never seen that before.
-For the cold salad?
-Sesame oil?
-Aekjeot, fish sauce.
-Aekjeot.
-Aekjeot?
-Sugar?
That must be the sour offal dish
he had mentioned.
He'll probably mix it with offal.
-What's that? Spinal cord?
-Spinal cord!
Beef spinal cord.
A jump rope.
I thought it'd go around his neck.
It's long enough to jump over.
I thought you were skipping rope.
That spinal cord looks so nice and chewy.
-It has to be especially fresh to eat.
-Exactly.
-You must love beef spinal cord.
-Yes.
He was very curious to see
how that dish would turn out.
He's scraping the pollack roe.
Pollack roe and beef spinal cord.
-He's mixing them.
-He's mixing them to make a cold dish.
7. MIX SPINAL CORD WITH POLLACK ROE,
GROUND PEPPER, AND MINCED GARLIC
AND THE KICK!
-What's that?
-Sea cucumber intestines.
-Sea cucumber.
THIS IS OFFAL TOO!
-Something smells good.
-It already smells delicious.
Yes, something smells so good.
-Are you grilling them this time?
-He puts them on the gridiron
-after pan-frying them once!
-That has to be good.
The visuals are killing it.
BANG!
That looks good.
-Ho-young!
-Flame-grilled!
-He's grilling them over the flame!
-It smells great, Ho-young!
It smells so good!
MOUTH-WATERING
It smells really great.
Are those burnt?
No, they're fine.
-Aren't those burnt?
-They look burnt.
-Open it and take a look.
-Cut it out.
-Open it.
Cut it out.
Whoa! Hey!
OPENED!
Doesn't that look burnt?
He's trying to hide it.
No, he's cutting the char off.
No, it's cooked perfectly.
Did anyone want it burnt?
You're pan-frying it again?
-You're pan-frying again?
-Again?
Yes, just for a bit.
He's going back and forth.
Sung-ju, can you report from the kitchen?
-Nam-no, five minutes.
-Five minutes.
Five minutes left.
Please report from the scene.
-Five minutes.
-It smells delicious.
My goodness.
-Gosh.
-Try this piece.
-This is for me?
-Yes.
What's this?
-What was it? What did you eat?
-The spinal cord?
-The spinal cord.
-What is this?
The spinal cord.
-The spinal cord.
Seasoned spinal cord.
There's zero funky smell
in the spinal cord.
It feels like soft gummy candy.
-Chewy.
-And it's refreshing.
-That sounds good.
-Very good.
Now, he gave me a piece of this.
What is it?
-Small intestine.
-Right?
All right. This one.
THE OFFAL DISH
HE LEARNED TO MAKE IN OSAKA!
Do you think the offal will get
a successful makeover?
OH, GOODNESS, MMM!
-Is it good?
-It's so good.
I love the fatty filling shooting out.
I love it.
You need that fatty filling.
8. ADD CHAR-GRILLED VEGGIES
-He's using the spinal cord too.
-Beef spinal cord!
He's using it too?
It's the topping.
You'll just top your dish with that?
Is that okay?
9. SEASON SPINAL CORD
WITH SALT, GARLIC, AND SESAME OIL
Gosh. Three minutes left.
I want to know
what the tomato soy sauce is like.
-The tomato soy sauce.
-This one?
The tomato… Yes.
It must be the sauce…
-It's the sauce, right?
-…for his cold dish.
Do you think Hang-jun will
save that flavor in his heart?
Well, I want to.
This is really good.
I think it could be a huge hit.
Isn't it too sweet?
-It's not sweet.
-No? Okay.
That was delicious and refreshing.
It also tastes healthy,
thanks to tomatoes.
Two minutes left.
-Two minutes.
-What's that? What's he adding?
-Beef heart.
-Beef heart!
Why are you adding it now?
-Beef heart. Does it have to go in later?
-It can become tough.
What's this soup?
-I made it with monkfish liver.
-Monkfish liver soup.
That's new.
-I see.
-Monkfish liver soup.
Ho-young tries it himself.
He studied in Osaka for three years!
-It must've been too salty.
-It's too salty.
-Too salty.
-Oh, man.
FEELING DIZZY
-That can be you soon.
-Exactly.
You can't spare a smile right now!
That can be you.
-I'm so nervous.
-Got it?
-It's too salty.
-Too salty?
But I like this light flavor.
-Wow.
-I like how it's different.
You just have to make it less salty.
You should taste it again
after he puts everything together.
-This one. I must taste it now.
-Yes.
-It's important.
-A minute and a half left.
Do you want to bring your offal to him?
Chef &…
SLAP
-…My Offal!
-My Offal!
-Chef & My Offal!
IN UNISON
This is great.
I love this one.
I'd like it to be spicier.
A bit spicier?
-Cheongyang pepper.
-It can be spicier. It's a bit too mild.
-That's it.
-Hurry up.
-The timer has turned red.
That one with the monkfish liver
looks really good.
NAM-NO BEGINS TO PLATE HIS DISH TOO
9. POUR THE JEONGOL IN A POT,
TOP WITH CHWINAMUL AND CHEONGYANG PEPPER
It's boiling. It looks so good.
One minute.
The timer has turned red.
Look at this. Nam-no is almost done too.
Can you taste his jeongol again?
It looks good.
This is insane.
How do they do this? Whoa.
This is Nam-no's dish
with only 40 seconds left.
Forty seconds left!
What's Nam-no's dish like?
HO-YOUNG FINISHES UP TOO
-Do you want to save that taste?
-Those two look similar.
TOPPING 2: SEASONED SPINAL CORD
CHECKING NAM-NO'S SOUP
There's a bit of a smell.
-There's a smell?
-Do you mind strong aromas?
-Ho-young finishes!
-When did you finish?
And Nam-no's done too!
YOON NAM-NO, JUNG HO-YOUNG
Whoa. When did they finish?
They both finished
with more than 20 seconds left.
WHOA…
Great job. That was fun.
Jeongol versus jeongol.
SERVE HIS MAJESTY'S MEALS!
ALL EYES ON THE DISHES
HALF AIR, HALF SMELL
All offal dishes
have been made for Hang-jun.
-Wow.
-Any thoughts?
It feels completely different
from watching this on the screen.
They do everything so smoothly,
yet I can still sense the urgency,
and on top of that, I can smell things.
My mouth kept watering,
so I just couldn't wait.
Please try Chef Ho-young's dish first.
Chef & My Offal.
A MAKEOVER PROJECT FOR OFFAL
A CLASSY HOT POT DISH
TOPPED WITH BEEF SPINAL CORD
CHEF JUNG HO-YOUNG'S CHEF & MY OFFAL
-He topped it with the spinal cord later.
-Thank you.
First, try the spinal cord
with the morning glory stir-fry.
Right below that is the doenjang broth
made with ground monkfish liver.
-So try it with a piece of intestine.
-That broth was good.
Spinal cord and morning glory.
No sauce?
I've seasoned it with salt and sesame oil.
-So there's no sauce.
-And morning glory.
Yes, the greens are seasoned too.
ALL EYES ON HIM
The guy who loves offal.
TURNING INTO A CAUTIOUS MALTESE DOG
It's uncomfortable
to bear all this attention.
TAKING A BITE WHILE CURLED UP
It must be your first time
having beef spinal cord like this, right?
It tastes completely different
with morning glory.
A MAKEOVER FOR THE SPINAL CORD
Since you love offal very much already,
I wanted to make it in a different style.
Is it seasoned well?
-It's perfect.
-It's perfectly seasoned.
It's very important
that the food is seasoned perfectly.
APPROVED
ANXIOUS
OFF TO A SMOOTH START
I'll try the small intestines.
-A piece of small intestine.
-Intestines.
-Small intestines are delicious.
-They are.
The fatty filling was so good.
GETTING EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
FROM THE FRONT AND THE SIDES
THE CAUTIOUS DOG RETURNS
Don't be so cautious. You've even
surpassed ten million admissions.
It's the first time
everyone in the room looked at me.
YOU'RE THE MAIN CHARACTER TODAY
I'm sure many people
have given you attention already.
Don't you think
you're ducking down too low?
He's hiding behind that pot.
-You're a legend now.
-Gosh.
-"Gosh."
BRIGHTENING UP
-Is it what you were looking for?
-Small intestines are perfect for this.
THEY MIX VERY WELL
The texture is just right too.
-I suggest that you try the soup.
-Sure.
-The soup.
-Made with doenjang
-and monkfish liver.
-That's right.
SLURPING ON THE SOUP
DEEPLY AMAZED
THE AMAZEMENT IS AS DEEP AS THE SOUP
ANOTHER SPOONFUL
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT!
-It's warm and nice.
-The soup must taste good.
THE 3RD TASTE
-Is it different from other soups?
-It's definitely different.
I've never had jeongol like this one.
The soup tastes somewhat familiar,
but in the end, it's new.
It's even more delicious
to think of the ingredients as I eat it.
Is there any funky smell?
-No, and actually, I…
-No?
Many chefs do their best
to get rid of funky smells,
but I even enjoy that smell.
-So he likes offal.
-Basically,
he likes all smells, aromas,
and even something that stinks.
He likes everything that smells.
THE LAST BITE
-It's delicious.
-It is?
-Next, please try Chef Nam-no's dish.
-Chef Nam-no.
COLD POLLACK ROE AND BEEF SPINAL CORD
AND ASSORTED OFFAL JEONGOL
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S SAVED YOU IN MY OFFAL
-Should he begin with the cold dish?
-Correct.
Which offal did you use for this one?
I mixed
beef spinal cord with pollack roe,
which is also considered offal, right?
I also topped it
with sea cucumber intestines.
ASSORTED OFFAL GIFT SET
It's a new kind of experience.
-And juiced tomatoes.
-With sea cucumber intestines.
He ate something long.
WIDE-EYED
-It's something that he'd love.
-He showed a big smile.
Sea cucumber intestines on top
was the smartest move.
-I see.
-He likes those things.
Otherwise, it would've been
something familiar,
but that addition
just made the dish more flavorful.
That was just the appetizer,
-but Nam-no already gets points.
-He seems to love it.
-He's taking huge bites.
-He likes it.
That means he really likes it.
I can tell that he loves it.
SAVORING
-It's good.
-It is.
He likes it.
PHEW
-Let's move on.
-Is there a ladle?
Back there, you said…
-You said that it smelled. What smell?
-I did.
-Like cilantro.
-That?
-He loves that smell.
-I do.
It must've been from the chwinamul.
Please pull that back
and dip the large intestines
in this sauce.
He's making use of it until the end.
Hang-jun liked it, so he's keeping it.
AND WHY NOT?
Nam-no seems a bit desperate.
-He's excited.
-He's in need.
The soup first.
What's the soup like?
That soup.
SLURP
It was a bit salty,
so he had to add some water.
-Is it good?
-It had a certain aroma.
It's the kind of flavor
I have never had before.
-But it's good.
-It is?
-I'm glad.
-It's something you've never had?
ARE THE INTESTINES DELICIOUS TOO?
-Was that sundae?
-Pi-sundae, Korean blood sausage.
ANXIOUS… NERVOUS…
Do you have to look?
WE WON'T LOOK, SO RELAX AND ENJOY
-We'll look away and chat.
-Let's chat.
We won't look.
Don't look that way.
He takes another bite while hiding.
He doesn't like attention.
A PIECE OF PI-SUNDAE GOES IN
GLANCES
He's still so cautious.
-He has an audience.
-And the soup.
-He took a huge bite.
-It's still hot!
-It's hot. Drink cold water.
-The pi-sundae is still hot.
-Gosh.
-"Gosh."
-This is good.
-It is?
ANOTHER BIG PRAISE
Let me try
the large intestine with chwinamul.
This time, I'll dip it in the sauce.
-He makes use of the tomato sauce.
-What's that like?
NODDING
-Was that good?
-It needs this sauce.
HEHE
I'M SO EXCITED♥
He did a great job with the sauce.
PRAISE MAKES HIM DANCE
Were there any other guests
who felt uncomfortable
with everyone's eyes on them?
Well, there were a few people,
but no one ate while hiding.
-There are small intestines too.
-Anything else?
DIPPING A PIECE OF SMALL INTESTINE
DIPPING A PIECE OF LARGE INTESTINE
-It must be great with the sea cucumber.
-He dips the large intestine.
-And pi-sundae.
-He's dipping everything.
He's dipping everything in the sauce.
-It must be great with everything.
-He must be so glad that he made it.
I'm so glad.
Does the flavor change with that sauce?
Yes, the meat still holds a bit of grease,
so this sauce helps
that greasy flavor disappear.
-So it balances it out.
-Yes.
VERY PLEASED
Would the two dishes be considered
different film genres?
-The ingredients are the same, right?
-Yes.
They're the same.
This one seems to be situated
-in a mountain village somewhere.
-A mountain village.
This one reminds me of a livestock farm.
-I see. Closer to civilization.
-Yes, that's right.
And now, let us have a taste too.
We'll begin with Chef Ho-young's dish.
Chef & My Offal.
I'LL TAKE ANOTHER BITE TOO
It's good.
It feels different to eat
beef spinal cord in this temperature.
-It's rich.
-Yes.
-It reminds me of jeotgal.
-It's monkfish liver.
A BITE, ANOTHER BITE
CAREFUL LIKE IT'S AN AUDITION
SOLEMN, STERN, SERIOUS
DID J. Y. PARK LIKE IT?
I produce singers, right?
What I do is hide their weakness
and bring out their strengths.
I don't actually create things.
And offal has such distinct pros and cons,
so it's a great dish if it brings out
the pros and hides the cons.
Beef spinal cord has its own flavor,
and the ingredients and the seasoning
he added are in line with that flavor.
Everything works in favor
of the spinal cord. It's fascinating.
ANXIOUS, BOWS
Jung-hwan says
the soup tastes like cutlassfish.
-It tastes like it.
-It's the monkfish.
-Is that it?
-The monkfish.
It tastes rich, as if he used
cutlassfish gut jeotgal for the soup.
But it's not too fishy.
He's famous
for his monkfish dishes, right?
-Monkfish Tiger.
-Monkfish Tiger returns.
Monkfish Tiger.
Director Yoo.
It looks like you're enjoying it.
It's delicious, but I'm getting worried.
-Why?
-How do you do this in 15 minutes?
Because he managed
to make this in 15 minutes?
Next, Chef Nam-no's dish,
Saved You in My Offal.
A BITE OF SEASONED POLLACK AND SPINAL CORD
-This is…
-It's like bulgogi.
This feels different.
WON'T STOP SCOOPING IT UP
CLEARED
He finished everything.
Did you like the other one too?
It wasn't the kind of taste
I expected from offal.
But I can't believe how he made
something this put together
in just 15 minutes.
HAPPY
I expected the tomato sauce
to taste refreshing and sour,
but he brought out the umami
like that of a rich broth.
It's salty and savory.
BROUGHT OUT THE POTENTIALS
The sourness
of the tomato sauce
reminds me of gazpacho,
which goes very well
with the greasy offal.
I see. They go well.
All right, then. It's time to choose.
Press one to choose Nam-no,
and two to choose Ho-young.
Which offal dish did you prefer?
You're not hiding your final choice.
SELECTIVE CAUTIOUSNESS?
OH, MY, MY
-He eats all hidden and chooses openly.
-Just like this?
He pressed a button.
Which one of them became the winner?
Let's find out who he chose.
Show us!
Which one of them will be
The Offal's Warden?
Will Ho-young beat Nam-no
and take his seventh star?
Or will Nam-no finally take a star
after four months?
Chang Hang-jun's choice!
Who did he side with?
Who's the winner?
Will it be Ho-young
who spent three years in Osaka? Or…
YOON NAM-NO WINS
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S
SAVED YOU IN MY OFFAL WINS
Yoon Nam-no!
Nam-no finally wins a star!
It's been four months!
-The first in four months!
-Should I be happy?
Congratulations, Nam-no.
The legend in the world of offal.
The legend in the world of offal?
-I really liked that he used chwinamul.
-Chwinamul.
Yes, definitely.
I thought the chwinamul aroma
blended nicely with the intestines.
Also, above all,
without this sauce…
-Yes.
-…he may not have won.
This was the biggest kick.
I'm so glad that I got to taste
something different like this.
It looks like Nam-no is misty-eyed.
-Don't cry, Nam-no.
-Nam-no.
His lips are pouty.
You've broken your losing streak.
How do you feel?
I should stay true to myself
and cook without thinking too much.
I'll keep staying true to myself.
-Good.
-Okay.
-Hang-jun chose Chef Nam-no.
-Great round.
-Put a star on him!
-Thank you.
-He was chosen by Hang-jun!
His second star!
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
Hang-jun's choice.
This is the second round of cook-off
with Hang-jun's ingredients.
The Italian master-pupil
that bond over their bluffs,
Chef Choi Hyun-suk and Kwon Sung-jun.
They make a great duo.
The Chinese sister chefs
who bond over their lunacy,
Chef Yi Moon-jung and Park Eun-yeong.
They seem like actual sisters.
-You're the same height.
-We are.
And they're the master and the pupil.
I hear Chef Hyun-suk
is deeply concerned about this round
-because of his partner, Sung-jun.
-Why?
I'm the type
who can be the star player on the show
that scores the winning goal,
-but at times, I can assist well too.
-Right.
I can sacrifice myself to light the room,
like a candle.
-But he's like a light bulb.
-A light bulb?
And one of those fairy lights at that.
What's important is that he shines.
ONLY HE WANTS TO STAND OUT
Do you agree with what he said?
He's spot on.
At least he doesn't lie.
As always, I plan to shine all alone.
But are you ready to show
good teamwork with Chef Hyun-suk?
People say that men
never forget their first love
and their first teacher.
So with my first master,
Chef Hyun-suk, right here,
I feel very confident.
I guess I was his master
for a very short period.
UGH…
But he knows
exactly what he must do to shine,
so I plan to support him fully.
What about the Chinese sister chefs?
I often saw people saying things like,
"What's going on with the women
in the world of Chinese cuisine?"
These days, right?
-So yes, we are the crazy sisters.
-The crazy sisters.
We acknowledge that.
I've kept my eyes on them
and came to realize
-they're possessed by evil spirits.
-Evil spirits?
They keep bringing them out
whenever they cook.
But then, Chef Hyun-suk
often sprinkles salt, right?
I think we should throw it that way
to cleanse them from the evil spirits.
-I see.
-So we'll sprinkle salt on them.
HMPH!
Chef Eun-yeong, did you feel the pressure
to play as a team with Moon-jung?
I've been suffering
from three losses in a row,
whereas Chef Moon-jung
has won three times in a row.
So if we lose this round,
I have a feeling that it'll be my fault.
-So that's a bit of pressure.
-Yes, you'd be criticized.
Just enjoy the moment.
Winning the star isn't important to me.
-Okay.
-Keep it up.
-Give her a hug.
-Let's show them.
HUG, GLANCE
That was so heartwarming.
Chef Sung-jun.
CHUCKLE
I don't care about winning the star.
-I just want you to shine.
-Okay.
That's it?
I shall shine.
TEAM MOON-JUNG & EUN-YEONG:
PORK BELLY, BONELESS CHICKEN THIGHS,
CARROT, SICHUAN JJAJANG RAMYEON SOUP BASE,
PIG'S TROTTER, PERILLA LEAF, AND MORE
What we've prepared today is called
WISWB.
-WISWB?
What matters
is the spirit that won't break?
What Matters Is that
Chinese Sister Chefs Won't Break.
Chinese Sister Chefs Won't Break, WISWB.
The King in The King's Warden
was in command of many,
but he…
SHE SUDDENLY BEGINS TO DANCE
She's doing that so suddenly.
SHE GOT INTO HER CHARACTER
DURING MOON-JUNG'S PRESENTATION…
BEGINS HER SOLO DANCE
-Please continue.
-He's…
-She's possessed.
-Did you plan this?
He's such a lonely man.
One day…
BOTH IN THEIR OWN TRANCES
EVEN DOING THE EXECUTIONER'S POSE
One day, I thought it'd be great
if he could sit with the people
-and have a drink with them.
-She's like an executioner.
-That's why…
-Gosh, Eun-yeong.
-That's the knife dance.
-She spurted water on the knife.
-We'll make Chinese wheat pancakes.
-Wheat pancakes.
-We'll serve them with your favorites,
-pork belly, seasoned pig's trotters…
-Seasoned pig's trotters.
…and stir-fried chicken.
You'll have fun making different wraps.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Also, we'll take down
those lousy Western cooks.
Then you can be called Chinese cooks!
That's awful. Lousy Western cooks?
That's one thing we hate to be called.
OTHER WESTERN COOKS ALSO GET TRIGGERED
They can't do anything without butter.
As Chinese cooks,
we prepared a good beating
-for those Western cooks.
-A good beating?
Despite the short amount of time,
-we'll also make a slushie.
-Slushie.
Without using a machine.
-Without a machine?
-She might use her knife.
The sisters will present our magic.
FULL OF EXPECTATION
TEAM HYUN-SUK & SUNG-JUN:
POMFRET, BLUE CRAB, SIRLOIN
PIG'S TROTTER, SWEET POTATO STEM,
CARROT, BREAD, ANCHOVY KAL-GUKSU SOUP BASE
Two Western cooks are up against them.
What are you two making?
-Your Majesty.
It Is Time to Dine on Pasta.
I'm so worried about them!
I'm so worried.
They're already on different pages.
-Wait, I got it.
-"Your Majesty."
-"It Is Time to Dine on Pasta."
"Time to Dine on Pasta."
What are you making?
-Your Majesty.
-It Is Time to Dine on Pasta.
-It Is Time to Dining Pasta.
It wasn't in sync. They should be exiled.
CHUCKLE
Your Majesty, It Is Time to Dine on Pasta.
He went on an exile,
and he could only find Western cooks
in the neighborhood.
INTRIGUED
And there, us Western cooks
-will beat the Chinese nobodies.
-Nobodies?
He just called you nobodies!
"Nobodies"?
What kind of pasta?
I want to challenge myself
and make fresh pasta within three minutes.
-In three minutes?
-Really?
-It'll be easy to pick.
-I'll make fresh pasta
to shine as the single fairy light.
To shine as the single fairy light?
-I'll make pasta similar to gujeolpan.
-Gujeolpan?
I'll make thin, fresh pasta
that'll be served cold
and add various toppings.
I'll use toppings like egg garnish
and sweet potato stems,
-like royal court cuisine.
-But it's pasta?
So pasta is your main dish?
-It's the appetizer.
-Pasta is the appetizer?
-I'll braise the pomfret as the main dish.
-Braised pomfret.
-It sounds good.
-It sounds great.
-Really?
-I'll bring out the tenderness,
while using Western cuisine techniques
to add different textures and inspire you.
And this braised pomfret
will taste like ggotge-tang.
-Whoa.
-But you won't make ggotge-tang?
-It'll taste like it?
-It'll be…
-Is he making bisque?
-…a nice dish for exhausted Hang-jun.
I want him to be inspired through this,
as well as be comforted
by the new experience.
MOVED
Let us begin the cook-off.
The timer, please.
Here to blow away
the bluffs of the Western cooks,
the lunatic and crazy
Chinese sister chefs,
Chef Yi Moon-jung and Park Eun-yeong.
They've come out well.
-They did.
-So well.
Here to cleanse
the lunacy of the Chinese sister chefs,
-the two Italian priests…
-I'll be like Sung-jun.
…Chef Choi Hyun-suk and Kwon Sung-jun.
Which dish will the exhausted Hang-jun
be more refreshed by?
It's a team round.
-Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
-Let's go!
-Begin!
HUGGING
TO THEIR POSITIONS AFTER THE HUG!
Let's go!
BOTH CHARGING FORWARD
He's prepping the pomfret first.
Hyun-suk's prepping the pomfret.
It's actually golden pompano,
which is much more expensive.
Hyun-suk cuts out
a piece of pomfret fillet.
All right.
WHAT'S THE FAIRY LIGHT UP TO?
-What did you put in?
-Sweet potato stems.
-What's that? Chives?
-Sweet potatoes?
-Sweet potato stems.
Sweet potato stems.
WHAT'S NEXT?
They're using blue crabs too.
-Ggotge-tang.
-They're going into the oven.
-Bisque.
-By roasting.
-And then make broth?
-I think so.
They're probably making bisque.
I put the bread in the pan, Master.
TAPPING
EGG
MAKING THE PASTA DOUGH!
Chef Sung-jun, we must salt this.
-Chef Sung-jun.
-No, not now!
-Fine. I'll sprinkle it alone.
-I can't do it now.
ON HIS OWN
I'll sprinkle it alone.
CLEANSING THEM ALONE
MISSING TEAMWORK
They promised to sprinkle salt together,
but he had to make the dough.
Sung-jun was so sure
he'd make fresh pasta in three minutes.
He's doing a challenge of his own.
-Fresh pasta in three minutes.
-Three minutes.
-It's been a minute and ten seconds.
-Yes.
THREATENING BY SHARPENING
Moon-jung begins by sharpening her knife.
BEGINS TO PREP PORK BELLY!
Chef Moon-jung
seems to be working with pork belly.
She's really quick with her hands.
-Yes, Chef Moon-jung is really fast.
-She is.
That's her strong suit.
NEXT, BONELESS CHICKEN THIGHS!
1. JULIENNE PORK BELLY
AND BONELESS CHICKEN THIGHS
FINISHED IN NO TIME!
ON TO THE NEXT TASK!
CHEONGYANG PEPPER, GREEN ONION
CARROT, ONION
GARLIC, PERILLA LEAVES
She's so fast.
Chef Eun-yeong
is making dough with hot water.
Is Eun-yeong also making dough?
It must be for the wheat pancakes.
They said they'd make those.
-They're using soup base.
-Ramyeon soup base?
-They're using ramyeon soup base?
-Anchovy kal-guksu soup base.
-That's a good one.
-Anchovy kal-guksu.
You have a minute and a half
to finish making the noodles.
BEGINS TO FLATTEN THE DOUGH
Sung-jun, are you almost done?
I'm almost done.
Really? Are you really done with it?
THE BREAD SUNG-JUN HAD THROWN IN
Chef Sung-jun.
-Where's the piping tip?
-Over here.
-It's here.
-Okay.
You were supposed to do this,
but I'll do it.
FISHING FOR COMPLIMENTS
FORMERLY SUNG-JUN'S JOB
-Always making sure he gets the credit.
-Right.
-"Not my job, but I'll do it for you."
-Yes, exactly.
Otherwise, no one will know.
That wasn't actually his job.
Sung-jun has 45 seconds
to finish the noodles!
-Okay.
-Forty-five seconds.
I had to do something else.
It seems almost done,
-but he pledged to do it in three minutes.
-Yes, he said it.
Chef Eun-yeong,
are you making wheat pancakes?
-Yes, these are for the wheat pancakes.
-They look good.
-Looking perfect.
-You're right.
Chinese chefs are always good
-at making flour dough.
-The sizes are the same.
WHAT'S MOON-JUNG UP TO?
It looks like Moon-jung added
some ramyeon soup base to the meat.
OYSTER SAUCE
She's really quick.
I wonder what Moon-jung
and Eun-yeong will make as a team.
BEEF BULGOGI MARINADE
-It's almost time.
-The pasta, Sung-jun!
-Six. Five.
-Come on, Sung-jun. Six.
-Seven. Six.
I DID IT
It's ready!
That took less than three minutes.
He made fresh pasta noodles.
-Sung-jun.
-You did it.
The lone fairy light lit up.
WATCH ME BURN
-Wait, it's too early.
-I'll wash it with cold water.
-What?
Okay.
What Chef Hyun-suk is doing
is a technique often used with potatoes.
-Sure.
-He's making scales
-with bread pieces.
-On top of the fish?
-Like the scales?
-You're right.
-They'll look like scales as it cooks.
Hang-jun is a filmmaker
who puts an emphasis on images,
so that can bring in extra points.
-The aesthetics are important.
-Yes.
-The visual beauty.
-Exactly.
Chef Eun-yeong is making wheat pancakes.
She's almost done with them too.
3. RUB SESAME OIL ON DOUGH DISCS,
STACK, THEN FLATTEN
Look how quick she is.
She's making pancakes quickly!
-Whoa!
-That's how you make them?
You're doing great!
SHE KNOWS HOW TO RAISE THE SPIRIT
Chef Eun-yeong knows
when to come in and shine
and when to step back and assist.
-When she must assist, she does that.
-She does.
-She quietly does her job.
-Yes.
-Ten minutes!
-Already?
What do we do? There's no time.
We don't have enough time.
CHOPPING THE INGREDIENTS
TO USE AS THE TOPPING!
5. JULIENNE SIRLOIN, CARROT
AND PIG'S TROTTERS
-Shouldn't you drain the pasta?
-I will!
-I'll do it.
-No, I got it.
I SHALL SHINE ALL ALONE
-Chef Sung-jun!
-Yes?
Let me know if you need help.
-Okay.
-I'll help you with anything.
He always demands compliments
after doing something that isn't his job.
GRILLING POMFRET WITH BREAD SCALES
Pot.
Where's the other pot?
-Which one?
-Where's the other pot?
-Pot? No idea.
-Is it over here?
COULDN'T CARE LESS IF IT ISN'T HIS JOB
-I found it.
-The pot.
POOR TEAMWORK,
JUST LIKE THEIR MISMATCHING LIMB LENGTHS
BAKED BLUE CRABS, OUT
I didn't use that pot.
Why is the heat so low?
QUICKLY COOKS THE CARROT
AND BEEF SIRLOIN
7. STIR-FRY BEEF SIRLOIN
WITH SOY SAUCE AND MINCED GARLIC
I need to make egg garnish.
WAS IN CHARGE OF EGG GARNISH
BUT FIRST, BLUE CRABS!
Nine minutes left!
EUN-YEONG BEGINS TO COOK THE PANCAKES!
Eun-yeong uses both hands.
USING BOTH HANDS
She's cooking two pieces at once.
She's really quick.
-The wheat pancakes look so good.
-Yes.
Pig's trotter?
-Pig's trotter.
-She's chopping it.
JULIENNING A PIG'S TROTTER TOO!
What's that for?
I'll season it.
They said they'd have him
make pancake wraps.
It'll become pancake filling.
-Moon-jung, I'm going to go.
-Wait.
Okay!
Go where, Eun-yeong?
-Here I go.
-Wait!
WHERE IS SHE GOING?
What are you doing?
Give them a good beating!
Give them a good
beating!
THE WHEAT PANCAKE SLAP
PERFECTLY SEPARATED INTO TWO
Yaho!
WHAT WAS THAT?
-Here we go again!
-Give him a good…
Give him a good
beating! Beat him!
She has to slap it.
WHEAT PANCAKE: STOP BEATING ME…
They're still stuck.
Yaho.
THE GYARU GHOST KEEPS POSSESSING HER
They make such a good team.
Yes, they're a great team.
-They have great teamwork.
-That's teamwork.
Right?
PUT A CLOTH ON TOP AND COOL
WHAT ABOUT TEAM WESTERN CUISINE
WITH ZERO TEAMWORK?
Chef, I think the fish is burning.
-What happened?
-No, Chef!
THE SCALES CAME OFF
No, I'll put them back on!
The fish scales
he tried so hard to stick on all fell off.
-The scales?
-The fish scales?
FALLING OFF…
I'll stick them back on later,
so be quiet!
-They all came off?
-They all did!
I will stick them back on, so be quiet!
POINTS FOR VISUALS: -10 POINTS
Why did you try
to make scales for the fish?
You said you'd make egg garnish.
Is it ready?
Egg garnish? I'm sorry. What now?
-Wait, Hyun-suk.
-What do we do?
I'll do it, Chef Hyun-suk.
-Let's do it together.
-Trust me.
-So the scales are gone?
-Yes, they're gone.
-The scales are charred!
-The scales!
-The scales.
-We're fine.
-We can do this.
-They're crunchy. Don't worry.
I'll just stick them on.
The scales look burnt.
-He puts them back on.
-I knew it.
Because they both burn brightly,
the scales got charred.
Six minutes and thirty seconds.
SUNG-JUN COVERS AND MAKES EGG GARNISH
TOSSING
-What's with the garnish?
-It looks odd.
Wait, what's with this?
I'll do the egg garnish.
You're going to do it?
HYUN-SUK IS IN CHARGE
OF THE EGG WHITE GARNISH
WHAT ABOUT SUNG-JUN'S EGG?
STARTING TO STICK TO THE PAN
It's an emergency.
-The egg garnish!
-The egg garnish is ruined!
-That was practice.
-It was ruined?
-It was a test.
-What test?
Lock them up!
IF IT WERE THE KING'S MEAL,
THEY'D BE IMPRISONED
-Lock them up in prison!
-They're heinous criminals!
Why are the scales dark?
Test success.
THANKFULLY,
THE WHITE GARNISH WAS A SUCCESS
The egg garnish.
TOSSING IT TO SUNG-JUN
Seven minutes.
Okay. We're fine.
Stay calm.
Season and toss it.
5. MIX PIG'S TROTTERS WITH BULDAK SAUCE,
VINEGAR, SUGAR, AND SESAME OIL
Eun-yeong is doing her part very well.
WHAT'S YI MOON-JUNG UP TO?
LOTS OF SALT ON ICE
AND A BOWL OVER THAT!
Moon-jung and Eun-yeong
are sailing smoothly.
Six minutes.
-What's in the bowl?
-What bowl?
-This one.
-This? It's the slushie.
-Slushie.
They must make slushie too.
Wait, you aren't using a blender?
-They don't have one.
-How are you going to shave ice?
-Five minutes.
-Okay.
Please go check, Jung-hwan.
Chinese cooks versus Western cooks.
-Jeez.
-Isn't it insane?
This is awesome.
And I've been doing this weekly.
-The team round moves much faster.
-It's insane, isn't it?
This is amazing.
I don't think I can…
-Chef Moon-jung!
-I'll stir-fry now.
-Stir-fry?
-You'll stir-fry that?
They don't have enough time.
The meat. We're good.
THE MEAT THEY MARINATED
They seem busy.
What's this?
-Seasoned pig's trotter.
-It's the filling.
-For the wrap, right?
She's stir-frying here,
and the pancakes are coming along nicely.
Where's the strainer?
The strainer?
-I got it.
-Okay.
-It's an emergency. Let's hurry.
-It's an emergency.
9. BOIL DOWN BLUE CRAB BROTH WITH BUTTER
-Egg garnish.
We only need a little.
Yes, we only need a bit.
CHOPPING EGG WHITE GARNISH
INTO THIN SLICES
JUST A TINY BIT
-The egg garnish.
-He ruined the first one, so it's a retry.
LOOKS LIKE QUAIL EGG GARNISH
Lock them up!
That's not an egg garnish!
It's a fried egg!
-It's a fried egg!
-That's not an egg garnish!
-It's not!
-Hyun-suk!
-It's not ruined.
-It's just a fried egg.
The garnish is only meant for His Majesty!
Hyun-suk insists it's not ruined.
-How do you call that egg garnish?
-That's a fried egg, not egg garnish!
Slow down.
The Chinese cooks have great teamwork.
-And they're quick.
-They work as a team
as they communicate.
Team Chinese is showing a better process.
ARGH!
She's stirring with one hand
and stir-frying with the other!
It's slowly freezing.
What? Really? It's starting to freeze?
-Can it freeze in time?
-It's freezing.
A TINY PIECE OF EGG YOLK GARNISH
It's a fried egg.
-How is that egg garnish?
-It is, once it's chopped!
He's chopping the fried egg
like it's a garnish!
Like it was an egg garnish!
The egg garnish looks great.
10. ADD OLIVE OIL AND SALT TO COOKED PASTA
TIME FOR MANTECARE
Now, the pasta.
-Pasta.
-Yes, separately.
Let me grill this over charcoal.
PLANS TO FLAME-GRILL THE CHICKEN!
You're using a lot of sauce.
She's stirring with one hand
and stir-frying with the other!
What are you doing? What's going on?
BURSTING INTO FLAMES
Chef Eun-yeong!
Simply starting a fire
can't make you shine!
I'm adding the smoky flavor!
This is the most complicated
kitchen situation
in the history of this show!
What's Eun-yeong cooking on the gridiron?
-Is this chicken?
-Boneless chicken thighs.
-One minute.
THIS TEAM BEGINS TO PLATE THE DISHES
Chef Sung-jun, salt, please!
ATTACKING FIRST
-Salt!
-Take this!
Take this!
PFFT…
THEIR LENGTH DIFFERENCE IS JUST CRUEL
Sung-jun's arm is so short
that he ended up salting Hyun-suk!
They're too far away.
WHAT ABOUT THE SALTED SHAMANS?
SPIRALING
Do this.
-A minute and 30 seconds.
-Here we go, Moon-jung.
A minute and 30 seconds.
GOING, GOING, GOING…
CHANNELING A SPIRIT…
WE'RE SO SCARED…
You're doing great!
Keep going!
Go! Stay strong!
Switch with me. Good!
Okay. We're done!
-Plate the dishes!
-We're done!
-Finish first to take the upper hand.
-Bring me the dish.
Wait, what are you doing?
What is it?
POURING INFUSED BLUE CRAB SAUCE
WHAT ABOUT THE LONE FAIRY LIGHT?
ADDING TOPPINGS ON THE PASTA
-Are you done?
-Almost.
-This, in the middle.
-The sauce.
-I'll ring the bell.
-Okay.
-I'll ring it!
-Wait!
-I'll ring it now!
-Okay!
-Are you serious?
-Are you really done?
-Are you done?
-Almost done.
-They're about to finish.
-I'm done.
Team Hyun-suk and Sung-jun finishes first.
They still had one minute left.
They finished with one minute to spare.
It's okay.
Let's make use of the remaining time.
They're already going second,
so they're using the full 15 minutes.
Keep it up, Chinese chefs!
-Keep it up.
-Let's go!
-Go.
-We didn't need 15 minutes.
-Ten seconds!
-Eight!
-Seven. Six. Five.
-Four. Three.
-Two. One.
-The end.
-We're done.
PESTERING WITH LONG LIMBS
I got it!
THE CHIHUAHUA WITH A SHARP TEMPER
Great job. It's all right.
BOTHERING WITH SHORT LIMBS
IT'S HECTIC UNTIL THE END
-And they're done.
-They're done!
Team Chinese is done.
-That was a hectic round.
-It's over.
Serve it with the ice bowl.
Can he drink it out of the straw?
SERVING THE ENTIRE BOWL
Are we on a vacation?
ON OUR WAY TO GIVE MORE ENERGY
TO EXHAUSTED HANG-JUN
It turned into slushie.
-How did it freeze?
-How did that happen?
AMAZED
Everything has been made
for exhausted Hang-jun.
That was a tense and dramatic round.
I never imagined cooking
could be so thrilling.
I was reminded of a horse race.
-Yes, a horse race.
-They only race forward.
"Horse number one. Horse number two."
Not only did they cook very quickly,
but they didn't forget
-to throw in humor in the process.
-Yes, that's what's important.
There were all kinds of emotions
and ups and downs.
They first burned something,
then found a way to cope with that.
-A renowned filmmaker would notice that.
-Yes.
Here's a thought I had
while watching this round.
"Yes, this is who we are as a people."
Is it strange
that I almost felt the patriotic hype
as I watched them?
You saw our potential.
"This is who we are as a people."
They came through everything
despite the worst conditions.
That was amazing.
All four sweated profusely
as they did their best.
-I can't wait to try these.
-You can't wait?
The two Western chefs finished first.
EGG YOLK, CARROT, SWEET POTATO STEM,
EGG WHITES, POLLACK ROE, SIRLOIN, TROTTERS
A FRESH PASTA DISH
PRESENTED LIKE GUJEOLPAN
BRAISED POMFRET
WITH PIECES OF BREAD SCALES
HYUN-SUK & SUNG-JUN'S
YOUR MAJESTY, IT IS TIME TO DINE ON PASTA
This one is the appetizer, right?
-Place them vertically aligned.
-Vertically.
SPINNING
-No, align the dishes vertically…
-The dishes.
…and place the pasta horizontally.
You've cooked long enough to know!
Okay. All right.
ONE MORE SERVING MISTAKE
AND THERE WILL BE TROUBLE
That's the appetizer.
-You can mix everything.
-Mix everything completely.
Mix everything?
They made cold pasta from scratch,
instead of using dried pasta.
-In three minutes.
-I wonder what that's like.
Pasta made faster than ramyeon.
-That's the appetizer.
-The pasta noodles.
Gujeolpan pasta.
He's really good at making pasta,
and he loves to eat it too.
-I should use chopsticks.
-Use chopsticks.
Your Majesty,
you'd better use chopsticks.
The King got exiled to a place
where only Western chefs lived.
-I love that backstory too.
-Sure.
At first, he didn't want it,
but he became too hungry.
If it's bad,
we'll send them back to their country.
So, Your Majesty, what do you think?
-Whoa.
-"Whoa."
The pasta noodles must be good.
I was just getting tired
and feeling drowsy,
-but this dish woke me up immediately.
-It did?
-The flavor that wakes you up.
-Yes.
He seems to like noodles.
MM-HMM
What's the pasta like?
It's excellent.
He made it in three minutes.
It's the kind of texture
that Koreans love.
I see. And it contains
many different ingredients.
AGAIN, ALL EYES ARE ON HIM
GLANCING
I keep getting conscious.
THE BIG SHOT FILMMAKER FEELS CAUTIOUS
Is there anything
they could've done better?
-If I must…
-If you must?
…point out a shortcoming,
it would be that
it needs a bit more umami.
Lash them!
The dish lacks umami!
Western cooks don't know how to add umami.
-Not yet.
-Not yet?
That's the appetizer,
so it can't be too strong.
It's just the appetizer.
-The umami.
-The main dish will explode with umami.
He saved it for the main dish.
-Let me…
-That's the main dish.
This is the main dish?
The main dish is a smaller portion
than the appetizer.
-Your Majesty, allow me to pour the sauce.
-The sauce.
Like that.
This is braised pomfret.
The portion reminds me
of a daycare kid's meal.
The scales
turned out like go stones.
They're go stones, not scales, right?
-He tried to depict fish scales.
-Not go stones?
Try it with the sauce.
They will be criminally charged
the moment he finds a bone.
We must lock them up.
-Gosh.
-Yes?
CURIOUS
-Your Majesty, do you like it?
-I knew it.
This dish
looked a little undersized when I saw it,
so I wasn't so impressed.
But the taste
-is just incredible.
-He's too good.
-Also, the scales.
-The bread.
They play a role in bringing out
the texture very nicely.
Pomfret tends to feel mushy when cooked,
but these add crunchiness.
The texture that boosts your mood
and makes the experience fun.
That was what Chef Hyun-suk was after.
Isn't it regular bread?
I wanted to create
different textures and flavors
within a single dish
to give you more inspiration.
STUMBLED OVER THE PRONUNCIATION
It's very delicious.
Next, WISWB.
FILL THE WHEAT PANCAKES WITH
PORK BELLY, CHICKEN, OR PIG'S TROTTER!
COLD SLUSHIE SERVED IN A BOWL
MOON-JUNG AND EUN-YEONG'S WISWB
Wait a second.
Did you mean to serve it like this?
Your Majesty.
Try to walk in your people's shoes
and drink it out of the straw,
straight from the bowl.
Straight from the bowl?
OH… VERY WELL!
Your Majesty, the people
are sipping it out of the bowl.
There were no straws back then.
HISTORICAL FALLACY
-So he's going to eat it with the pancake?
-The pancake.
-Chicken is the lightest and the cleanest.
-The center.
-The center. The pale one.
-The pale one in the center.
-This…
-Make a wrap with it first.
See if it's been seasoned well.
Try all three fillings,
then make a wrap with your favorite one.
A BITE OF JUST THE CHICKEN STIR-FRY
Eun-yeong worked very hard
stir-frying everything.
He's using both hands.
-It's delicious.
-He says it's delicious.
-Should he try everything?
-Sure.
What's that one?
What you grabbed is jingjiang rousi,
sauteed pork in sweet sauce.
-Jingjiang rousi.
-It's a meat stir-fry dish
cooked with chunjang.
But you didn't have chunjang,
so we improvised
and used
Sichuan jjajang ramyeon soup base.
Jjajang ramyeon soup base?
-Using ramyeon soup base is like cheating.
-I see.
THEY USED SOME TOO…
His Majesty enjoys ramyeon soup base.
That's why it's darker in color.
Jingjiang rousi.
Actually, Hang-jun is someone
who finds making wraps troublesome.
OH…
He doesn't like making wraps.
Ah-ha.
Whoa.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Is it all right? Are you pleased?
It's spicy and delicious.
-It's spicy?
-It is.
-It's the Sichuan version.
-Sichuan jjajang ramyeon.
It was the Sichuan version.
I saw you using Buldak sauce too.
It's in the schweinshaxe,
the pig's trotter dish.
-Schweinshaxe?
-That's schweinshaxe?
-Schweinshaxe for the King?
That is a German dish, Your Majesty.
But it's not all Buldak sauce.
We just added a hint of it.
It's probably spicy.
WHAT'S SEASONED PIG'S TROTTER LIKE?
He's about to eat it.
-This looks like the main dish.
-Wrap it.
-The pig's trotter.
-He'll like this one.
GULP
He seems pleased.
This schweinshaxe is the best.
-Among the three?
-Yes.
It's nicely spicy, and I love the texture.
We used just the skin
to let you enjoy the chewy texture.
Let me make a wrap
with all three fillings.
Please try it like that.
-You can mix them up too.
-It looks great.
However you'd like.
It's a Chinese-style dish.
-All three fillings.
-He has a tiny mouth.
-Yes, in one pancake.
-I do.
You don't have to eat the whole thing.
You can take small bites.
It's tough to keep his dignity
while eating that.
-Let's give him some time to chew.
-We should.
His mouth is full.
-I wonder what the mix is like.
-I wonder.
Does it taste like a German film?
There are all kinds of emotions,
love, friendship,
poetic justice, and everything.
But there's one thing.
It would've been better
if one characteristic stood out.
DISAPPOINTED
-Try the slushie too.
-Right, the slushie.
LOOKS REFRESHINGLY COLD
-The slushie.
What did you use?
-Soju.
-Soju?
-It has alcohol?
-There's alcohol?
Yes, I mixed soju, lemon-lime soda,
and blueberry juice.
It should be a little sweet,
but we thought you would need
that sugar rush
-around this hour.
-Yes, I can feel the rush.
And how can I put this?
It's clearing up my head.
It must be the soju.
-Is that so?
-I guess so.
SOJU IS PERFECT AFTER AN EXHAUSTING DAY
-It's thanks to soju.
-It's soju.
I don't usually like
eating anything this sweet,
-but this one is good.
-That means…
How did the liquid turn into a slushie?
Ice and salt create thermal conduction,
so it freezes the liquid
and creates a slushie.
-It's science.
-It was scientific.
-It's time to choose.
-Yes.
It was a team round,
so two people will get one star each.
Please make a careful decision.
Press one for Moon-jung and Eun-yeong,
Team Chinese Cuisine.
Press two for Hyun-suk and Sung-jun,
Team Western Cuisine.
Make your decision and press the button!
PICKED ONE IMMEDIATELY
-I did.
-Already?
-That was fast.
Are you the type
who usually decides quickly?
There are millions of decisions
to be made in my line of work.
The moment I step out of my car,
-the staff bombard me with questions.
-On what to do?
At most, I have to make
200 to 300 decisions a day,
and quickly too.
-Otherwise, the shoot gets delayed.
-Right.
Or was one side much better?
-It was very close.
-Very close.
-You just always decide quickly.
-Yes.
All right.
Let's find out the result. Show us!
A Dish for Exhausted Hang-jun.
Which side is it?
Is it Western cuisine
or Chinese cuisine?
Is it Hyun-suk and Sung-jun,
the master and the pupil?
or is it Moon-jung and Eun-yeong,
the sisters?
Which side is it?
Which dish was more comforting?
Who made you happier?
CHOI HYUN-SUK AND KWON SUNG-JUN WIN
KWON SUNG-JUN & CHOI HYUN-SUK WIN
Hyun-suk and Sung-jun!
-I knew it.
-It was Western cuisine.
That's my master.
THE BRIGHTLY DAZZLING LONE FAIRY LIGHT
Chef Hyun-suk sheds the light
solely on his student,
his junior chef and his pupil.
SHINE EVEN BRIGHTER
-He lets him take the spotlight.
-And he just takes it.
He's something.
What was the difference?
Chef Moon-jung and Eun-yeong's dish
was also very delicious.
-I see.
-Especially
-the schweinshaxe.
-Schweinshaxe.
If you served that dish alone,
-Rather?
-it could have changed
the entire plotline.
As for the Western cuisine,
I did not expect anything
-from that kid-sized pomfret.
-Kid-sized pomfret?
Were the scales made with bread?
Those scales gave the fish
such a nice spirit.
THANK YOU
-That was the key.
-The scales.
I'm not sure
who did more to win that star,
but let's hear from them.
We had such great teamwork today.
Also, we split up the task at first,
but unforeseen circumstances always arise.
The scales that he just complimented
were supposed to be cut out by Sung-jun,
but I did it.
I believe we won
because Sung-jun did a great job.
HE DOESN'T EVEN MEAN IT
That didn't quite add up.
Actually, Hang-jun said it accurately.
The fish dish could grab the attention
because I didn't
season the pasta too much.
You made that room.
I did.
It played its role as the appetizer.
When I just listen to you two,
you sound like a typical scammer duo.
You exaggerate so much.
This means the Western chefs have won.
Please put the stars on them.
-Wow.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Congrats.
-One each for the two.
Smile a little.
-It's okay.
-I can't smile.
This means Hyun-suk now has eight stars
and Sung-jun has seven stars.
Eight wins, seven wins.
They chase right after the lead.
Congratulations!
-They have lots of stars.
-Western cuisine wins!
It's the 33rd year since his debut.
I'm in my best physical condition.
Where do you get this kind of energy?
I put all my money and effort
into my diet.
-We present his fridge!
-Fridge!
WOW
I'm already seeing
lots of "organic" labels.
His freezer's empty.
The thing is,
he's not prepared for an emergency.
He'll have to starve.
A cook-off for J. Y. Park.
There's fish, and there's meat.
IT ALREADY LOOKS HEALTHY
They're both desperate for a star.
-Wake up!
-Emergency!
It's an emergency.
Be quiet.
Sam's mad.
Poached eggs are great for pockets.
I'll use tenderloin
to let you sound tender.
He's dying to be funny.
THE ROAD TO KIM POONG IS NOT OVER
THE TWO UNORTHODOX COOKS
FACE EACH OTHER
YOO YONG-WOOK, THE BARBECUE EXPERT,
MAKES A SMOKY, EXPLOSIVE DEBUT
THE ORIGINAL UNORTHODOX COOK, KIM POONG
Please! The deity of Chef & My Fridge!
Please be our witness!
THIS TIME, HE DID SOMETHING BIG…
That's insane!
Whoa.
How can it taste like this?
MOVED
WHICH DISH CAPTURED J. Y. PARK'S HEART?
-It's good.
-He's too moved.
This is a difficult time for us, everyone!
We seriously need high ratings!
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn